mygreencorner.com 2015-12-17

# Privacy policy

Mygreencorner.com is the sole owner of the information collected on Mygreencorner.com. 

We will not disclose your information to any third parties. This Web site takes every precaution to protect our users' information. When users submit sensitive information via the Web site, their information is protected both online and off-line.

We collect information from our users at several different points on our Web site:

  * Registration - to our Theme Viewer, Css Template viewer of Wp Market - we use this information to contact the user about services on our site or on other sites, you agree with this upon registration.
  * Submit service - we require information from the user on our submit form - we use this information to contact the user about services on our site or on other sites, you agree with this upon submission.
  * Contact Form - we require information from the user on our contact form - we use this information to contact the user about services on our site or on other sites, you agree with this upon contacting us.

Though we make every effort to preserve user privacy, we may need to disclose personal information when required by law wherein we have a good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with a current judicial proceeding, a court order or legal process served on our Web site.

If a user's personally identifiable information changes (such as zip code, phone, email or postal address or site), or if a user no longer desires our service, we provide a way to correct or update users' personally identifiable information. This can be done by using our contact page.

If users have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us.

Google adsense disclaimer:

  * Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on this site.
  * Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to sites on the Internet.
  * Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.
